



Bru Mas Ribera

About

Frontend & UX Engineer from Barcelona. Based in Meiringen, Switzerland

8+ years of professional experience

Website

SKILLS & TOOLS

Languages TypeScript, JavaScript, Python **Frontend** React, Next.js, Vue, Tailwind CSS Backend Node.js, Django, Supabase **UX** tools Figma, Storybook, User Research

ABOUT ME

Computer Engineer specialized in Web Development with 6 years Frontend and 3 years Backend experience. UX Designer with 3 years experience.

Successfully delivered ESA-funded Proof of Concept, coordinating international consortiums.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2014 - Present • Remote

Founder & Project Lead | Open Huts, Booking Platform for Nature Huts

Find hidden places to sleep out in the wild. Help protect nature by enjoying it. User research, prototyping, user testing, hi-fi interfaces with Figma and implementation with React, Next.js, TypeScript, Supabase

2021 – 2024 • Remote

Frontend & UX Engineer | Moodle, Open Learning Platform

Developing MoodleNet, a network to share and curate open educational resources. Using React, Figma, UX Design, Open Source, Educational Technology

2020 • Lausanne, Switzerland

User Experience Designer | Oberalp Group, Pomoca

Redesigning the production interfaces of the ski touring skins world leader, Pomoca. Behavioral Interviewing, Usability Testing, UX Design, **Production Interfaces**

2017 - 2018 • Remote

Junior Web Developer | Pix4D, Photogrammetry for Construction and Agriculture

Developing a cloud platform to upload, process and analyze 3D models from drone images. Angular 4, RxJS, Cloud Platform, 3D Modeling, **Drone Technology**

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021

MBA

ThePowerMBA

2020

User Experience Design

Udacity

2014 - 2018

BA Computer Engineering

Barcelona University

2014 - 2018

Architecture

UPC, Barcelona

LANGUAGES

C2: English, French • Native: Spanish, Catalan

C1: Italian • B1: German, Portuguese

INTERESTS

Business Development Environment Restoration

SKILL SET

UIMLA Mountain Leader User Research & Testing

CONTACT

☑ Email in LinkedIn ♀ GitHub ⊕ bru.masribera.com